Anthony Burke-Hall

anthonybhall1@gmail.com | 321-987-4043 | Palm Bay, FL | LinkedIn | GitHub | Portfolio

SUMMARY

Passionate HTML Email Developer with a keen eye for design and a drive to create engaging user experiences. Utilizing an agile methodology to reach development deadlines. Using Microsoft Teams to communicate with teammates in an agile environment. And to deliver the project smoothly by writing clean HTML and CSS that is effective and functional.

EXPERIENCE

INVESTCLOUD | JR. FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER | Tampa, FL | Mar 2022 - Mar 2023

- Collaborated with 8 team members to identify site objectives and user needs, using Microsoft Teams and creating user-friendly website experiences with 15% more engagement
- Performed quality assurance (QA) checks on average per project, discovering bugs and communicating concerns to other designers, improving efficiency and user experience throughout the life cycle of a project
- Focused on building site functionality with HTML, CSS, and tracking tickets with Jira Orchestrated a seamless project management process by implementing an agile workflow; conducted daily stand-ups, sprint reviews, and retrospectives that reduced development time by 20% and increased client satisfaction by 35%
- Pushed code base with Tortoise SVN (Version control), to move tested code to the project

COMPSYS | PRODUCTION TECH | Melbourne, FL | Oct 2020 - Mar 2022

- Working with a team to reach deadlines
- Producing materials at company standards
- Adapting to changing company needs to make projected customer needs
- Operate fiberglass production tools
- Monitor quality control
- Maintain equipment and workspace

BUFFALO WILD WINGS | LINE COOK | Melbourne, FL | Feb 2016 - Mar 2019

- Followed OSHA(Occupational Safety and Health Administration) standards
- Communicated with the front of the house to deliver food safely and promptly to customers
- Organized kitchen staff to perform tasks effectively and orderly throughout their shift

EDUCATION

BAYSIDE HIGHSCHOOL | DIPLOMA Palm Bay, FL | Aug 2011 - Jun 2015 GPA: 3.2

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- GITHUB
- MAIL CHIMP

- SYSTEM PERFORMANCE
- BEHAVIOR MANAGEMENT
- TESTING AND QA OF EMAIL IN MULTIPLE BROWSERS
- EMAIL DESIGN
- PHOTOSHOP

PROJECTS

PROMO EMAIL | Link

This HTML email uses CSS tables to create a responsive email advertisement compatible with all major email clients.

TRANSACTION EMAIL | Link

The transactional email is a mock email that a customer would receive after purchasing. The email features the purchase item, price, and order number.

DICE GAME | Link

This frontend application utilizes jQuery to create the logic to randomize the dice roll when the user clicks the button. And also changes the font to match the result of the dice roll.

NEWSLETTER | Link

Full-stack app that incorporates CSS, HTML, JavaScript, and Node.js with the API from Mail chimp to create an email list web application.

TINDOG (Tinder Clone) | Link

Tindog is a beautiful landing page for a mock Tinder landing page. This website was created with CSS, HTML, and Bootstrap. And demonstrates the elegant design of a modern landing page that can help drive sales.